What I’m hearing
repeatedly from our customers
is that they’re looking for fewer,
more strategic relationships
with their trusted partners
around the world.
The incredible thing
about our organization,
our unmatched breadth and depth
puts us in a position
that we can be
one of those key strategic partners.
Having a more
coordinated approach to market
allows us to put our best foot
forward to our customers.
It allows us to deliver
unparalleled customer experience.
No other competitor has the assets,
the technology or the people,
and we need
to share this with our customers.
That’s what this is about.
Today, in Thomson Reuters,
we have best practices
that are sprinkled
across the organization
in terms of going to market.
If we were able to pull
all those best practices together,
we would be a formidable force
in the marketplace.
The biggest challenge for me
with the way we currently
approach sales operations
is that we do it in a vacuum.
We can’t get out of our own way.
Right now, our reps
are spending entirely too much time
on administrative tasks,
which is taking them away
from spending time
where they should be spending it.
Which is in front of our customers.
Today, we do not get
a significant percentage of our leads
through the demand generation
and marketing channel.
Roughly 10 to 11 percent,
and that could be higher.
I think a coordinated
go-to-market strategy for retention
would be extremely compelling.
It means our customers
will derive much more value
from our platforms.
It would mean that they’d
be able to navigate
the uncertainty
in their respective businesses
that they face nowadays.
A coordinated global approach
to enterprise selling
is a unique opportunity to grow
and to serve our customers better.
We need to have a common vocabulary,
a common lexicon
and a common way
of talking about customers.
It’s really about developing
a common view of our customers
and better understanding
what their needs are.
Really, we want to show the world
that Thomson Reuters is by far
the most global, the most scalable,
the most comprehensive solution
and trusted partner for solving
our customers’ biggest problems.
Our customers are asking for it,
our markets are demanding it.
The difference for us
is being just successful,
or being wildly successful.
I think
there’s a profound responsibility
that goes with the trust
our customers have in us.
I take that very, very seriously.
They are relying on us for the most
important questions they face
and that carries with it
an obligation on our part,
that we make sure
we get it absolutely right.